<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
	<data>
		<!-- Template for Header and Footer -->
		<template id="external_layout_stspl_sales_report_template">
			<!-- Multicompany -->
			<t t-if="o and 'company_id' in o">
				<t t-set="company" t-value="o.company_id"></t>
			</t>
			<t t-if="not o or not 'company_id' in o">
				<t t-set="company" t-value="res_company"></t>
			</t>

			<t t-raw="0" />
			<t t-call="stspl_sales.external_layout_footer_stspl_sales_report_template" />
		</template>

		<!-- Footer for Sales Report -->
		<template id="external_layout_footer_stspl_sales_report_template">
			<div class="footer">
				<div class="last-page">
				    <div class="row">
						<div class="col-xs-4 pull-right" style="font-size:11.5px">
							<table class="table table-condensed">
								<tr>
									<td>Sub-Total</td>
									<td class="text-right">
										<span t-field="o.amount_untaxed" />
									</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>Discount</td>
									<td>
										<span />
									</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td>GST ZR 0%</td>
									<td class="text-right">
										<span t-field="o.amount_tax" />
									</td>
								</tr>
								<tr>
									<td><b>Total</b></td>
									<td class="text-right">
										<span t-field="o.amount_total" />
									</td>
								</tr>
							</table>
						</div>
					</div>
					<div style="text-align:left;font-size:10px;">
						<u>
							<p>Note:</p>
						</u>
						<p t-if="o.partner_id.comment"><span t-field="o.partner_id.comment"/></p>
	        		</div>


					<table style="border-top:1px solid;font-size:12px;" width="100%">
						<tr>
							<td width="80%">
								<div>
									<span>Please visit our website @ </span>
									<span t-field="o.company_id.website" />
								</div>
								<div>
									<span>email : </span>
									<span t-field="o.company_id.email" />
								</div>
								<br/>
								<div>
									<span>This is a computer generated documents and no signature is
										required
									</span>
								</div>
							</td>
							<td width="20%">
								<br/>
								<ul class="list-inline" style='text-align:right'>
									<li>Page:</li>
									<li>
										<span class="page" />
									</li>
									<li>/</li>
									<li>
										<span class="topage" />
									</li>
								</ul>
							</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</div>

				<div style="page-break-before:always;font-size:9.5px">
					<style>
						OL { counter-reset: item }
						LI { display: block }
						LI:before {
						content: counters(item, ".") " "; counter-increment: item }
					</style>

					<u style="font-size:13px">
						<strong>
							<center>STANDARD TERMS AND CONDITIONS</center>
						</strong>
					</u>
					<ol>
						<li>
							<strong>AGREEMENT OF SALE:</strong>

							<p>
								These Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale (“Terms”) shall
								apply
								to Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
								(“Seller”)
								Quotation,Acknowledgment or Invoice in which these
								Terms are
								specifically incorporated by reference (the
								Quotation,
								Acknowledgment, or Invoice together with these
								Terms, the
								“Agreement”). All purchases by Buyer of product and
								or
								services described in the Agreement (collectively, the
								“Product”) are expressly limited to and conditioned upon
								acceptance of these Terms, regardless of whether Buyer
								purchases such Product through any media or means,including
								but limited to, verbal or written purchase orders, electronic
								orders, acknowledgments, confirmations, or other writings from
								Buyer to Seller.
							</p>
							<p>
								Unless such provisions are expressly agreed to by Seller in
								a
								writing signed by Seller, any additional or conflicting terms
								and conditions contained on,attached to or referenced in
								Buyer’s writings, or other prior or later communication from
								Buyer to Seller, shall have no effect on the purchase of any
								such Product by Buyer from Seller and are expressly rejected
								by Seller.
							</p>

							<p>
								These Terms along with the Quotation, Acknowledgment or
								Invoice in
								which they are incorporated by reference are deemed
								an offer
								for sale by Seller.If Buyer does not accept in writing
								Seller’s offer to sell, Buyer’s commencement of performance
								(including ordering, purchases or taking delivery of or
								accepting Product) shall, in all cases, constitute Buyer’s
								unqualified and unconditional acceptance of the Agreement. Any
								conduct by Buyer which recognizes the existence of a contract
								pertaining to the subject matter hereof shall constitute
								acceptance by Buyer of this Agreement and all of its
								Terms.Additional or different terms provided in Buyer’s
								purchase order or any other documentation from Buyer which
								vary in any degree from any of the Terms here in are hereby
								objected to and rejected.
							</p>
							<p>
								These Terms may be modified from time to time by Seller, by
								notice
								to Buyer. Each such modification shall be binding upon
								Buyer
								with respect to all purchases occurring after the date of
								such
								modification. Except as otherwise described herein, no
								modification or termination hereof or waiver of any of the
								obligations hereunder shall be effective unless in writing and
								signed by the party against whom such modification,
								termination or waiver is sought to be enforced.
							</p>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>CONFIDENTIALITY:</strong>
							<ol type="decimal">
								<li> Buyer covenants that it will hold in trust and confidence
									any and all information of a confidential nature regarding
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd’s business or
									affairs, including, without limitation data provided by
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd regarding the
									design of the Products, and will not divulge, disclose, or in
									any way distribute to anyone, except to employees with a need
									to make use of such proprietary information.
								</li>
								<li>Buyer shall protect such proprietary information from
									disclosure to others with the same degree of care that a
									reasonable, diligent and prudent person would exercise in
									protecting its own confidential information of like
									sensitivity.
								</li>
								<li>
									The foregoing obligation shall not be applicable if Buyer can
									demonstrate by an appropriate document that such information:
									<ol type="i">
										<li>was already or later became, through no fault of Buyer,
											generally available to the public
										</li>
										<li>was already known to Buyer prior to the disclosure
											thereof by Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
										</li>
										<li>Or has lawfully become known to Buyer through a third
											party.
										</li>
									</ol>
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>VALIDITY:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>All quotations are valid for 30 days, unless specified.
								</li>
								<li>Once a quote has passed the expiry date, Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd may cancel the quote without
									having to notify or receive an approval from customer.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>SPECIFICATION:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>All goods supplied by us shall be in accordance with the
									quotation given and any further specifications or
									descriptions agreed or expressly listed or set out on the
									face of the order.
								</li>
								<li>We must be informed in writing within 30 days of
									acceptance of the quotation of any changes, alterations, or
									reductions.
								</li>
								<li>If Buyer requests changes in specifications or designs
									relating to any Product to be provided hereunder, shipment
									schedules shall be revised,if necessary, and an equitable
									adjustment, upward or downward, shall be made in price.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>PRICING:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>The price in the final quotation may vary from the
									original price if there are any price or product changes
									requested by customers.
								</li>
								<li>We endeavor to honor every prices quoted, if there is a
									price increase that is beyond our control, we reserve the
									right to increase the price as necessary.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>SHIPMENT FEES, GST, VAT AND TAXES:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Prices listed are exclusive of all transportation,
									insurance, license fees, customs duties, VAT, GST or any
									other duties or taxes which may be chargeable in connection
									with the supply of the products to Buyer, unless other
									specific terms are shown on the quotation.
								</li>
								<li>Any such tax, fee, or charge of any nature whatsoever
									designated, levied, based or imposed by any governmental
									authority on, or measured by, the transaction between
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd and Buyer shall
									be paid by Buyer in addition to the prices quoted or
									invoiced.
								</li>
								<li>In the event Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
									pays any such tax, fee, or charge, at the time of sale or
									thereafter, Buyer shall promptly reimburse Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>NO MODIFICATION:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>This quotation is complete as written, and no changes,
									amendment or modification shall be made to this quotation
									without a separate written quotation from Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>ACCEPTANCE:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>On acceptance of the quotation by placing an order within
									the specified period as of the quotation, you will be bound
									by these terms and conditions stated. Each quotation accepted
									shall constitute an individual legally binding contract
									between you and us. Such contract is hereinafter referred to
									in these terms and conditions as "an order".
								</li>
								<li>Please ensure that our quotation number and the
									description on the quote to be the same as the one on the PO
									to avoid any misunderstanding of parts required.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>CANCELLATION:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Buyer acknowledges that any Product being purchased
									hereunder is being manufactured especially for Buyer. In no
									event shall Buyer have the right to cancel, modify or delay
									any order, except with Seller’s written consent and subject
									to conditions then to be agreed upon, which shall include
									protection of Seller against all losses.
								</li>
								<li>We reserve the right to retain any deposits or charge in
									full for any cancellation of PO, depending on the duration of
									cancellation made after PO was issued.
								</li>
								<li>
									Cancellation of an order for the convenience of the customer
									will result in the following charges:
									<table width="70%" border="1 px solid black">
										<tr>
											<th>Milestone</th>
											<th>Charge</th>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td>Receipt of order prior to start of engineering</td>
											<td>0%</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td>Completion of engineering</td>
											<td>25%</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td>Completion of procurement</td>
											<td>50%</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td>Completion of sub-assemblies</td>
											<td>75%</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td>Completion of manufacturing</td>
											<td>100%</td>
										</tr>
									</table>
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>DELIVERY</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd will try to
									ensure compliance with any delivery times and dates given,
									but such times and dates are an estimate only. We will not be
									responsible for any loss whatsoever arising from or
									consequential upon delay in delivery.
								</li>
								<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd have the
									right to make partial shipments, and each partial shipment
									shall be deemed a separate sale, and payment shall become due
									therefore in accordance with the terms of payment as of the
									quotation, unless otherwise specified.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>INCOTERMS:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Unless this Agreement expressly provides otherwise, the
									Terms used in this Agreement shall have the meanings set
									forth in INCOTERMS 2010, as published and promulgated by the
									International Chamber of Commerce.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>TITLE AND RISK OF LOSS:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Notwithstanding any shipping term, title to any Product
									sold and risk of loss of such Product passes to Buyer upon
									delivery by Seller to the carrier and Product shall be deemed
									“delivered” at such time, and any claims for losses or damage
									occurring after delivery to carrier by Seller shall be made
									by Buyer directly with the carrier.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>PAYMENT:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>If payment hereunder is not made on time, Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd, in addition to all other
									legal, equitable and contract rights, shall be entitled to
									interest on such overdue payment at the rate of 2% (two
									percent) per month.
								</li>
								<li>Notwithstanding the foregoing, interest shall not be
									charged on any overdue payment at a rate in excess of the
									maximum rate permitted by law.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>WARRANTY:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd warrants that
									the Product will conform, at the time of delivery to Buyer,
									to the Agreement specifications specified in the quotation,
									order acknowledgment, or invoice.
								</li>
								<li>In the case of Product bought from Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd unable to conform,
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd will offer
									repair or exchange, solely if the cause of disability is due
									to manufacturing reasons.
								</li>
								<li>If any form of repair or consultation from Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd is required, the service will
									be chargeable and cost has to be agreed before any form of
									repair or consultation takes place.
								</li>
								<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd and Buyer
									expressly agree that the product excludes any form of
									arranty, guarantees, or representations, expressed or
									implied, of compatibility for a particular purpose or use.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>FAILURE ANALYSIS</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>
									If Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd determines,
									while analyzing your product, that repairs are needed due to
									failures of parts that are neither supplied nor repaired by
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore or are needed due to
									damage caused by misuse or misapplication, Semiconductor
									Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd reserves the right to return
									the product to you without repairing it, and will hold you
									responsible for the diagnostic fee, shipment charges, plus
									any applicable tax and also all other charges that are
									involved in the process.
									<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd may hold you
										responsible for the diagnostic fee, shipment charges, plus
										any applicable tax,and all other charges involved in the
										process if Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
										performs an analysis on your product,provides a quotation to
										you, and you do not authorize Semiconductor Technologies
										Singapore Pte Ltd to undertake the repairs for the quoted
										charges.
									</li>
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>REPAIR AND EVALUATION:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>Unless your product is repaired under warranty, you will
									be required to pay Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte
									Ltd.
								</li>
								<li>Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd will issue a
									quotation for the repair cost. Sending out the equipment to
									Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd for repair
									denotes the quoted pricing for repair is agreeable.
								</li>
								<li>Your payment is due when the product is returned to you
									unless specified otherwise.
								</li>
								<li>The quoted amount will be an estimate and will be liable
									to changes. It includes all parts, labor, and shipment
									required for the repair of the product plus any applicable
									tax.
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
						<li>
							<strong>SERVICE:</strong>
							<ol>
								<li>
									In the event the services of a Semiconductor Technologies
									Singapore Pte Ltd required to provide field work or
									assistance to include, but not be limited to, installation,
									supervision, training of personnel, etc., following
									conditions applies:
									<ol>
										<li>
											Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd shall
											furnish technical and
											professional services as may be
											required including
											labor,transportation, and supervision and
											shall perform all
											operations necessary and required to
											satisfactorily provide
											technical assistance and direction to
											the customer during
											the installation, start-up, and/or
											training of
											Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
											furnished
											equipment, as may be requested.
										</li>
										<li>
											Materials, supplies and equipment may either be supplied
											by
											Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd or buyer, to
											be determined at such time that a contract for field
											service work is initiated.
										</li>
										<li>
											Upon Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd
											completion of
											work at the site, Semiconductor Technologies
											Singapore Pte
											Ltd shall submit a trip report, documenting
											dates at the
											site, people contacted, activities, problems
											observed, and
											inspection performed by field personnel.
										</li>
										<li>
											Field Service Orders require customers to FAX a Purchase
											Order
											to Semiconductor Technologies Singapore Pte Ltd prior
											to
											the departure of the Service Engineer to the jobsite.
											Work
											performed due to defective material or workmanship
											within
											limitations of the standard warranty will be
											performed at
											no charge, subject to the inspection of
											products.
										</li>
									</ol>
								</li>
							</ol>
						</li>
					</ol>
				</div>
			
			</div>
		</template>

		<template id="report.minimal_layout">
            <t t-raw="'&lt;base href=%s&gt;' % base_url"/>
            &lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;
                <html style="height: 0;">
                    <head>
                        <link href="/report/static/src/css/reset.min.css" rel="stylesheet"/>
                        <link href="/web/static/lib/bootstrap/css/bootstrap.css" rel="stylesheet"/>
                        <link href="/website/static/src/css/website.css" rel="stylesheet"/>
                        <link href="/web/static/lib/fontawesome/css/font-awesome.css" rel="stylesheet"/>
                        <style type='text/css'><t t-raw="css"/></style>
                        <t t-if="subst is True">
                            		        <script>
                       function subst() {
                           var vars = {};
                           var x = document.location.search.substring(1).split('&amp;');
                           for (var i in x) {
                               var z = x[i].split('=', 2);
                               vars[z[0]] = unescape(z[1]);
                           }
                           var x=['frompage', 'topage', 'page', 'webpage', 'section', 'subsection', 'subsubsection'];
                           for (var i in x) {
                               var y = document.getElementsByClassName(x[i]);
                               for (var j=0; j&lt;y.length; ++j)
                                   y[j].textContent = vars[x[i]];
                           }
                           var operations = {
    							'last-page': function (elt) { elt.style.visibility = (vars.page === vars.topage) ? "visible" : "hidden"; },
							};

                           for (var klass in operations) {
                               var y = document.getElementsByClassName(klass);
                               for (var j=0; j&lt;y.length; ++j)
                               operations[klass](y[j]);
                           }
                      }
                  </script>
                        </t>
                    </head>
                    <body class="container" onload="subst()">
                        <t t-raw="body"/>
                    </body>
                </html>
         </template>

		<!-- Template for Sales Order Report -->
		<template id="sgtpl_sale_report_template">
			<style type="text/css">
				td.line , span.line ,th.line {
				font-family:times new
				roman;
				}
			</style>
			<t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-call="stspl_sales.external_layout_stspl_sales_report_template">
					<div class="page">
						<div class="oe_structure" />
						<div class="row">
							<div class="col-xs-3">
								<span t-if="o.company_id and o.company_id.logo">
									<img t-att-src="'data:image/png;base64,%s' % o.company_id.logo"
										style="max-height: 75px;" />
								</span>
							</div>
							<div class="col-xs-8 col-xs-offset-1 text-right">
								<div t-if="o.company_id" style="font-size:12px">
									<div>
										<h5><b><span t-field="o.company_id.name"></span></b></h5>
									</div>
									<div>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.street"/>
										,
										<span t-field="o.company_id.city"/>
										,
										<span t-field="o.company_id.country_id"/>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.zip"/>
									</div>

									<div>
										<span>Tel :</span>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.phone" />

										<span>Fax :</span>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.fax" />
									</div>
									<div>
										<span>CO. REG. NO. </span>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.company_registry" />
									</div>
									<div>
										<span class="text-right">GST REG NO. </span>
										<span t-field="o.company_id.gst_no" />
									</div>
								</div>
							</div>
						</div>
						<br/>
						<div class="row">
							<div class="col-xs-7" style="font-size:12px">
								<h4 t-if="o.state == 'draft'"><b>QUOTATION</b></h4>
								<h4 t-if="o.state != 'draft'"><b>SALES ORDER</b></h4>

								<td width="60%">
									<span>TO:</span>
									<div t-if="o.partner_id ">
										<div t-field="o.partner_id" />
										<div t-field="o.partner_id.street" />
										<div t-field="o.partner_id.city" />
										<div t-field="o.partner_id.state_id" />
										<div t-field="o.partner_id.country_id" />
									</div>
									<br/>
									<div>
										<span>ATTN:</span><span style="padding:25px" t-field="o.user_id"/><br/>
										<span>C.C:</span><span style="padding:25px" t-field="o.partner_id.website"/><br/>
										<span>TEL:</span><span style="padding:25px" t-field="o.partner_id.phone"/><br/>
									</div>
								</td>
							</div>

							<div class="col-xs-5 text-right">
                   				<div style="font-size:13px">
                   					<span>NO.</span>
                   					<strong><span style="padding:82px" t-esc="get_quat(o.date_order,o.name)"/></strong>
                   				</div>
                   				<div style="font-size:12px">
                   					<span>DATE</span><span style="padding:59px" t-field="o.date_order" t-field-options='{"format": "dd-MM-Y HH:MM:SS"}' />
                   				</div>

                   				<td width="55%">
									<table style="font-size:11px">
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>YourRef   </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span t-field="o.client_order_ref" />
											</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Incoterms  </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span t-field="o.incoterm.code" />
											</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Payment Term  </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span t-field="o.payment_term" />
											</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Lead Time</span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px"></td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Sales Person   </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span t-field="o.user_id.name" />
											</td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Validity   </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px"></td>
										</tr>
										<tr>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span>Currency  </span>
											</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">:</td>
											<td style="padding:5px">
												<span t-field="o.currency_id" />
											</td>
										</tr>
									</table>
								</td>
		                  	</div>
						</div>
						<br />

						<table class="table table-condensed" width="100%" style="border-top:0.5px solid;font-size:11px;">
							<thead>
								<tr>
									<th t-if="o.state == 'draft'" width="12%">Item No</th>
									<th t-if="o.state != 'draft'" width="12%">Serial No.</th>
									<th class="text-center line" width="35%">Description/Part No</th>
									<th t-if="o.state != 'draft'" class="text-left line" width="13%">ETD</th>
									<th class="text-left line" width="5%">Qty</th>
									<th class="text-left line" width="10%">Units</th>
									<th class="text-right line" width="15%">Unit Price</th>
									<th class="text-right line" width="10%">Amount</th>
								</tr>
							</thead>
							<tbody>
								<tr t-foreach="o.order_line" t-as="line">
									<td t-if="o.state == 'draft'" width="12%" class="text-center line">
										<span t-esc="line_index+1" />
									</td>
									<td t-if="o.state != 'draft'" width="12%" class="text-center line">
										<span t-esc="line_index+1" />
									</td>
									<td class="text-left line" width="35%">
										<t t-if="line.product_id">
											<span t-field="line.product_id.name" />
											:
											<span t-field="line.product_id.description" />
										</t>
									</td>
									<td t-if="o.state != 'draft'" class="text-left line" width="12%">
										<t t-if="o.picking_ids and line.product_id">
											<span t-esc="get_etd(o.picking_ids,line.product_id)" />
										</t>
									</td>
									<td class="text-left line" width="5%">
										<span t-esc="get_qty(line.product_uom_qty)" />
									</td>
									<td class="text-left line" width="10%">
										<span t-field="line.product_uom.name" />
									</td>
									<td class="text-right line" width="15%">
										<span t-field="line.price_unit" />
									</td>
									<td class="text-right line" width="10%">
										<span t-field="line.price_subtotal" />
									</td>
								</tr>
							</tbody>
						</table>						
					</div>
				</t>
			</t>
		</template>

		<template id="report_sale_order">
			<t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-foreach="doc_ids" t-as="doc_id">
					<t
						t-raw="translate_doc(doc_id, doc_model, 'partner_id.lang', 'stspl_sales.sgtpl_sale_report_template')" />
				</t>
			</t>
		</template>
	</data>
</openerp>
